Text samples from The "anyone can be provincial!" page :
http://www.trigeminal.com/samples/provincial.html
لماذا لا يتكلمون اللّغة العربية فحسب؟
Защо те просто не могат да говорят български?
Per què no poden simplement parlar en català?
他們爲什麽不說中文（台灣）？
Proč prostě nemluví česky?
Hvorfor kan de ikke bare tale dansk?
Warum sprechen sie nicht einfach Deutsch?
Μα γιατί δεν μπορούν να μιλήσουν Ελληνικά;
Why can't they just speak English?
¿Por qué no pueden simplemente hablar en castellano?
Miksi he eivät yksinkertaisesti puhu suomea?
Pourquoi, tout simplement, ne parlent-ils pas français ?
למה הם פשוט לא מדברים עברית?
Miért nem beszélnek egyszerűen magyarul?
Af hverju geta þeir ekki bara talað íslensku?
Perché non possono semplicemente parlare italiano?
なぜ、みんな日本語を話してくれないのか？
세계의 모든 사람들이 한국어를 이해한다면 얼마나 좋을까?
Waarom spreken ze niet gewoon Nederlands?
Hvorfor kan de ikke bare snakke norsk?
Dlaczego oni po prostu nie mówią po polsku?
Porque é que eles não falam em Português (do Brasil)?
Oare astia de ce nu vorbesc româneşte?
Почему же они не говорят по-русски?
Zašto jednostavno ne govore hrvatski?
Pse nuk duan të flasin vetëm shqip?
Varför pratar dom inte bara svenska?
ทำไมเขาถึงไม่พูดภาษาไทย
Neden Türkçe konuşamıyorlar?
Mengapa mereka tidak bisa bicara bahasa Indonesia?
Чому б їм не розмовляти українською?
Чаму яны не гавораць па-беларуску?
Zakaj vendar ne govorijo slovensko?
Kāpēc viņi vienkārši nerunā latviski?
Kodėl gi jie nekalba lietuviškai?
Čaro onho ba zaboni točiki gap namezanand?
خب، چرا فارسى صحبت نمى كنند؟
Tại sao họ không thể chỉ nói tiếng Việt?
Ինչու՞ նրանք չեն խոսում Հայերեն
Zergatik ezin dute Euzkeraz bakarrik hitzegin?
Čehodla da woni serbsce njerěča?
Зошто тие едноставно не говорат македонски?
Waarom kan hulle nie net doodgewoon Afrikaans praat nie?
რატომ არ ლაპარაკობენ ისინი ქართულად?
यह लोग हिन्दी क्यों नहीं बोल सकते हैं ?
Carson nach eil iad a'bruidhinn na Gàidhlige?
פֿאַרװאָס רעדט מען ניט פּשוט ייִדיש?
Олар неге қазақ тiлiнде сойлемейдi?
Емне үчүн алар кыргызча сүйлбйт?
Nega ular uzbek tilinda gapirmaidilar?
Нишләп олар татарча сүләша алмыйлар?
ওরা েকন বাংলা বলেত পাের না ?
બદ્ધા લોકો ગુજરાતી કૅમ નથી બોલતા?
ସେମାନେ ଉଡିଯାରେ କହିନ୍କି କହିବେ ନହିଁ?
அவர்கள் ஏன் தமிழில் பேசக்கூடாது ?
తెలుగులో ఎందుకు మాట్లాడరు?
ಅವರು ಕನ್ನಡ ಮಾತನಾಡಬಹುದಲ್ಲಾ?
लोकांना मराठी का बोलता येत नाही?
ते किं संस्कृतः माम वदन्ति ?
ག་རེ་བྱས་ཁོ་རང་ཚོས་བོད་སྐད་ཆ་དེ་ག་རང་བཤད་ཀྱི་མ་རེད།
Pam dydyn nhw ddim yn siarad Cymraeg?
¿Por que non poden simplemente falar en galego?
ಕಒಂಕಣಇ ಕಸಲಯಆಕ ಉಲಐನಾ ?
ܠܡܢܐܠܐܡܡܠܠܝܢܣܘܪܝܝܐ؟
අැයි ඔවුන්ට ඉංගරිස කතා ෛනබ ?
ᓱᒻᒪᓂᒃᑯᐊ ᐃᓄᑦᑎᑐᑐᐃᓐᓇᔭᙱᓚᑦ
ለምንድነው አማርኛ የማይናገሩት፧
Bakit hindi na lang sila magsalita ng Tagalog?
qatlh tlhIngan Hol lujatlhlaHbe' neH
Prag a yl ý ewn a gows kernewek?
Ciin kiingan Yugcetun qalarcuitat?
Sapay nga dida la agsao ti Ilokanon?
Anongkot kari kai lay nan magsalita nin Zambale?
Kátse násh nu zburáscu Armánesche?
Soske ola na kerena lafi Romane?
Wieso kenne die ned änfach pälzisch sprooche ?
לְמָה לָא יאמרוּן בְּאַרָמִית?
Маг1арул мац1алда гьел щай к1алъаларел?
Arapa ma'ta' nganggui basa Madura bai?
Kenapa kok ora nganggo basa Jawa wae?
Хьунд оцярг нохчи кхамял ца дало?
Worom kennad dia ned oifach schwäbisch schwätza?
Warum kenna de ned oafach boarisch re’n?
He aha ai  kore ratou e korero Maori noa iho !
demeuz weijnaeng baugangj vahcuengh?
Gbe fa mia vi teh de Mendeyie huu?
Kial oni simple ne parolas Esperanton?
Ma perchè poeuden minga semplicement parlà milanes?
他们为什么不说中文（中国）？
Wieso chönne dia nöd iefach schwizerdütsch redda?
¿Por qué no pueden simplemente hablar Español de México?
Kunnen ze geen Vlaams spreken?
Kvifor kan dei ikkje berre snakke nynorsk?
Porque é que eles não falam simplesmente em Português?
De ce ei nu vorbesc moldoveneşte?
Zašto jednostavno ne govore srpski?
Нийя онлар азярбайжан дилиндя данышмырлар?
Cén fáth nach labhrann siad as Gaeilge?
Нега улар узбек тилинда гапирмайдилар?
उनीहरू किन नेपाली मात्र बोल्न सक्दैनन् ?
KAX XIFAN HOL LUJAXBE' NEH
Aponapa ma'ta' ngagam basa Madura saos?
Kenging punapa kok mboten ngagem Basa Jawi Kemawon?
ليه ما بتكلموش عربي؟
他們爲什麽不說中文（香港特別行政區）？
Wye carnay jus stalk Strine?
¿Por qué no pueden simplemente hablar en Español?
Pourquoi? y parlent pas français?
Зашто они једноставно не говоре Српски?
他们为什么不说中文（新加坡）
Woufir schwätzen si net einfach Letzebuergesch?
¿Por qué no pueden simplemente hablar Español de Guatemala?
Zašto jednostavno ne govore bosanski?
他們爲什麽不說中文（澳門特別行政區）？
ليش ماعم بيحكو عربي؟
¿Por qué no pueden simplemente hablar Español de Argentina?
ليش ما يتكلمون عربيعلى الأقل؟
أو ليش ما تتكلمون عربي؟
Bon sak fè ke yo paka pale Kreyòl?
وليش بس ما يحكوا عربي؟
Διὰ τὶ οὐ δύνανται τὴν Ἑλληνικὴν λαλεῖν ;
מדוע לא דברו עברית?
Чаро онҳо ба забони точики гап намезананд?
Ⴐატომ Ⴀრ Ⴊაპარაკობენ Ⴈსინი Ⴕქართულად ?
Olar nege khazakh tilinde soilemeidi?
ᓱᒻᒪᓂᒃᑯᐊ ᐃᓄᒃᑎᑐᑐᐃᓐᓇᔭᙱᓚᑦ